{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What is the treble clef also known as?"
  "incorrect": [
    "E Clef",
    "F Clef",
    "H Clef"
  ],
  "correct": "G Clef"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What is the bass clef also known as?"
  "incorrect": [
    "E Clef",
    "G Clef",
    "H Clef"
  ],
  "correct": "F Clef"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What is the G clef also known as?"
  "incorrect": [
    "Bass Clef",
    "Alto Clef",
    "Tenor Clef"
  ],
  "correct": "Treble Clef"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What is the F clef also known as?"
  "incorrect": [
    "Treble Clef",
    "Alto Clef",
    "Tenor Clef"
  ],
  "correct": "Bass Clef"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What are the notes on the treble clef lines?"
  "incorrect": [
    "E, G, D, B, F",
    "E, B, G, D, F",
    "F, G, B, D, E"
  ],
  "correct": "E, G, B, D, F"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What are the notes on the treble clef spaces?"
  "incorrect": [
    "F, A, E, C",
    "F, C, A, E",
    "E, A, C, F"
  ],
  "correct": "F, A, C, E"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What are the notes on the bass clef lines?"
  "incorrect": [
    "G, B, F, D, A",
    "G, D, B, F, A",
    "A, B, D, F, G"
  ],
  "correct": "G, B, D, F, A"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What are the notes on the bass clef spaces?"
  "incorrect": [
    "A, C, G, E",
    "A, E, C, G",
    "G, C, E, A"
  ],
  "correct": "A, C, E, G"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What does a sharp do?"
  "incorrect": [
    "Makes the note last longer",
    "Cancels any exisitng accidentals",
    "Lower a note by one semitone"
  ],
  "correct": "Raise a note by one semitone"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What does a flat do?"
  "incorrect": [
    "Makes the note last longer",
    "Cancels any exisitng accidentals",
    "Raise a note by one semitone"
  ],
  "correct": "Lower a note by one semitone"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What does a natural do?"
  "incorrect": [
    "Makes the note last longer",
    "Lower a note by one semitone",
    "Raise a note by one semitone"
  ],
  "correct": "Cancels any exisitng accidentals"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What is the symbol for a sharp?"
  "incorrect": [
    "S",
    "♮",
    "♭"
  ],
  "correct": "#"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What is the symbol for a flat?"
  "incorrect": [
    "F",
    "♮",
    "#"
  ],
  "correct": "♭"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "stave",
  "question": "What is the symbol for a natural?"
  "incorrect": [
    "N",
    "♭",
    "#"
  ],
  "correct": "♮"
}
